T. DYLAN MEYERS

Highlands Ranch, CO ◆ C: 303-834-7439 ◆ meyers.dylan@outlook.com ◆ LinkedIn ◆ Github

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Detail-oriented software engineer with a diverse skill set in web development, front-end, and back-end technologies. Experienced in troubleshooting complex issues while providing empathy and collaborative communication. Demonstrated ability to resolve problems in a timely manner and escalate issues in forward-thinking and fluid environments. Enthusiastic to continue learning in order to contribute to F.O.S.S Projects.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, Javascript
- REACT, JSX
- Object-Oriented Programming

- CRUD, MERN
- RESTful API, MVC
- Git, GitHub
- INDUCES

- Windows 7, 8, & 10
- Active Directory, Azure
- Microsoft Office
- Google Productivity

EXPERIENCE

Help Desk Technician - Truist Bank - 12/2021 - 03/2023

- Conducted root-cause analysis and documented reasons for recurring technical issues, resulting in reduced downtime for internal banking systems.
- Achieved consistent performance above KPIs with a 98% rating in volume and customer survey scores.
- Administered new and existing user accounts using Active Directory.

Desktop Technician – Optistar Technologies, Inc – 06/2020 – 05/2021

- Successfully transfered network server of parent company hosting critical software and provided ongoing support.
- Provided Tier I & II end-user support for system issues, tracked resolutions, and performed root cause analysis.
- Managed users and inventory through Active Directory and Azure.

Service Desk Technician – SM Energy – 04/2019 – 04/2020

- Successfully facilitated the transfer of 300+ users to remote environments, utilizing Citrix Desktops.
- Independently researched and diagnosed complex problems while providing Tier I & II level end-user support for system issues
- Collaborated with Security to review User Access Protocols adherence, ensuring compliance and proper systems access via Active Directory and Azure

Projects

Cave Explorer – Browser Game – <u>Github</u>

- Independent project, creating a deliverable browser-based game in five days.
- Implemented using HTML, CSS, and Javascript.
- Focused on creating a flexible and responsive layout to maintain the intended feel across various screen sizes.

D&D Compendium - REACT Site - Github

- Independent project, creating a full REACT app with REDUX and external API consumption in five days.
- Implemented using REACT, VITE, REDUX and Material UI
- Focused on ease of navigation and managing state through REDUX while consuming data heavy API.

Cat-A-Base – MERN stack – Github

- Independent project, creating a live site with MERN stack.
- Implemented with MongoDB, Express, REACT, Node.JS, and external API
- Focused on user authentication and verification and multiple data entities interacting.

EDUCATION

- Software Engineering bootcamp
 - 15 weeks completing on September 8th
 - Focusing on full-stack development
- CompTia A+ Certification: March 2017